(Penny:)The one with the frogs.
(Penny:)It was pretty cool. A lot of the girls
threw up. I gutted that thing like a deer.
No. I'm sorry, Penny. I don't think so.
Oh, come on, a smart guy like you?
It'll be a challenge.
You could make it like an experiment.
(Leonard:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)I suppose if someone could teach
sign language to Koko the gorilla...
(Sheldon:)...I could teach you
some rudimentary physics.
Great. It's a little insulting, but great.
I'll be Koko.
Mm. Not likely. Koko learned to understand
over 2000 words.
(Sheldon:)Not one of which
had anything to do with shoes.
(Howard:)Hey, fellas,
this is my girlfriend, Bernadette.
(Howard(arriving):)My girlfriend, Bernadette.
(Bernadette:)-Who are all those people?
-I have no idea.
(Penny:)-Hey, Leonard.
-Hi.
(Leonard:)Look, it's Howard
and his girlfriend, Bernadette.
(Howard:)Thought I'd give the little woman
a tour of the old salt mines. Heh.
(Bernadette:)He doesn't mean salt mines.
He means where he works.